{
    "subject": "resource/Sister_Act",
    "predicate": "ontology/director",
    "object": "resource/Emile_Ardolino",
    "human_readable": "The director of Sister Act is Emile Ardolino.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8636972904205322,
            "question": "Which movie was directed by Emile Ardolino?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8462328314781189,
            "question": "Emile Ardolino is known for directing which film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7968745231628418,
            "question": "Who directed the movie Sister Act?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7875864505767822,
            "question": "Who was responsible for directing Sister Act?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7591274976730347,
            "question": "What is the name of the director of Sister Act?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7121261358261108,
            "question": "Emile Ardolino is the director of which popular comedy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6898711323738098,
            "question": "Name the director behind the musical Sister Act."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6548184156417847,
            "question": "What film is associated with Emile Ardolino?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6283340454101562,
            "question": "Can you tell me the director of the movie Sister Act?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5874882936477661,
            "question": "What film did Emile Ardolino direct?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The director of Sister Act is Emile Ardolino.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3308_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me the director of the movie Sister Act?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3308_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What film is associated with Emile Ardolino?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3308_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the director behind the musical Sister Act.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3308_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3308_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3308_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3308_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3308_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3308_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3308_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3308_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3308_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3308_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3308_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support this triple. Emile Ardolino is mentioned as the director of Sister Act in several documents, including file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3308/re-ranker-msmarco/5.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3308/re-ranker-msmarco/108.txt."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Emile Ardolino was the director of Sister Act (1992). Therefore, the triple \"The director of Sister Act is Emile Ardolino\" is correct according to the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}